<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dillon Pelster&#39;s Big_12 Sports Blog</title>
    <link>http://dpelster3.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dillon Pelster&#39;s Big_12 Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dpelster3.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Boston Celtics are Surging, Buckle Up Folks </title>
      <link>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/04/28/the-boston-celtics-are-surging-buckle-up-folks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/04/28/the-boston-celtics-are-surging-buckle-up-folks/</guid>
      <description>The Boston Celtics have been one of the better teams in the NBA for more than a half decade now, appearing in three of the last five Eastern Conference Finals. The Celtics window of title contention appeared to be solidified for the next decade after the 2018 Eastern Conference Finals, when then rookie Jayson Tatum, along with Jaylon Brown in his second year, took the league by stormed, taking Lebron James and the Cleveland Cavaliers to the brink of elimination, going toe-to-toe for seven games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big 12 has Staked Their Claim as the Best Conference in College Basketball</title>
      <link>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/04/08/the-big-12-has-staked-their-claim-as-the-best-conference-in-college-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/04/08/the-big-12-has-staked-their-claim-as-the-best-conference-in-college-basketball/</guid>
      <description>The 2021-2022 College Basketball season has come to a conclusion, with Bill Self and the Kansas Jayhawks securing their 4th National Title for the historic program in record breaking fashion, overcoming a 15 point halftime deficit, marking the largest comeback win in championship game history.For the second consecutive year, the Big 12 Conference has taken home the title, and after this run by the Jayhawks, it marks the 4th consecutive tournament where a Big 12 team has represented the league in the Final Four, along with five out of the last six.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://dpelster3.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dpelster3.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Dillon Pelster. On my own behalf, thank you for checking out my blog covering the Big 12 Conference and their basketball teams. As a double major in sports media communication and broadcasting, sports are at the center of my core values. My burning passion for sports resides in a lot of different areas, along with the games itself. My focus on this project was to find something to articulate with data relating to College Basketball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Chalk</title>
      <link>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/03/24/rock-chalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dpelster3.github.io/2022/03/24/rock-chalk/</guid>
      <description>This is my cool blog post about the jayhawks</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
